<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20170131</CreaDate><CreaTime>12443700</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><ArcGISstyle>Item Description</ArcGISstyle><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20170201</ModDate><ModTime>12463800</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange><ArcGISProfile>ItemDescription</ArcGISProfile></Esri><dataIdInfo><idPurp>Maps at a scale of 1:24,000 used to identify surficial geologic materials and resources, to identify and evaluate physical hazards, and to evaluate groundwater resources.</idPurp><idAbs>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Digital data from VG09-6 Springston, G. and Wright, S., 2009, Surficial geologic map of Charlotte, Vermont: Vermont Geological Survey Open-File Report VG09-6, 1 plate, scale 1:24,000. Data may include surficial geologic contacts, isopach contours lines, bedrock outcrop polygons, bedrock geologic contacts, hydrogeologic units and more. The surficial geologic materials data at a scale of 1:24,000 depict types of unconsolidated surficial and glacial materials overlying bedrock in Vermont. Data is created by mapping on the ground using standard geologic pace and compass techniques and/or GPS on a USGS 1:24000 topographic base map. The materials data is selected from the Vermont Geological Survey Open File Report (OFR) publication &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;(http://dec.vermont.gov/geological-survey/publication-gis/ofr)&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;. The OFR contains more complete descriptions of map units, cross-sections, isopach maps and other information that may not be included in this digital data set.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</idAbs><idCredit>VG09-6 Springston, G. and Wright, S., 2009, Surficial geologic map of Charlotte, Vermont: Vermont Geological Survey Open-File Report VG09-6, 1 plate, scale 1:24,000.</idCredit><idCitation><resTitle>Surficial geologic map of Charlotte, Vermont</resTitle></idCitation><searchKeys><keyword>Charlotte</keyword><keyword>Vermont</keyword><keyword>Vermont Geological Survey</keyword><keyword>Surficial Geology</keyword></searchKeys><resConst><Consts><useLimit>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The accuracy of the data layers is limited by the accuracy of the source materials. Data is intended to be used at the 1:24000 scale. Although every effort has been made to assure accuracy of features and attributes, the VT ANR is not responsible for errors in or misuse of the data. No warranty of accuracy or usefulness of data is implied or expressed.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</useLimit></Consts></resConst></dataIdInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv></metadata>
